Guide to the Records of the Office of External Affairs, Commencement and Special Events RG.7.4
New York University Archives
- Series III: Commencement, 241380
  - Commencement Addresses, 1930, 1933-1939; 241677 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Program, 1930; 241678 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Program, 1934; 241679 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Program, 1938; 241680 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Commencement Program, 1939; 241681 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Commencement Addresses, 1940-1942; 241682 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Commencement Program, 1940; 241683 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Commencement Program, 1941; 241684 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Commencement Program, 1942; 241685 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1943; 241686 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Commencement Program, 1944; 241687 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1945; 241688 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1946; 241689 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Commencement Program, 1946; 241690 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Commencement Addresses, 1947-1949; 241691 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Commencement Programs, 1947; 241692 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Commencement Program, 1948; 241693 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Commencement Program, 1949; 241694 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1950; 241695 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Commencement Programs, 1950; 241696 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Commencement Programs, 1951; 241697 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1952; 241698 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Commencement Program, 1952; 241699 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1953; 241700 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Commencement Programs, 1953; 241701 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1954; 241702 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Commencement Programs, 1954; 241703 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1954; 241704 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1955; 241705 (Box 39, Folder 32)
  - Commencement Programs, 1955; 241706 (Box 39, Folder 33)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1956; 241707 (Box 39, Folder 34)
  - Commencement Programs, 1956; 241708 (Box 39, Folder 35)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1956; 241709 (Box 39, Folder 36)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1957; 241710 (Box 39, Folder 37)
  - Commencement Programs, 1957; 241711 (Box 39, Folder 38)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1958; 241712 (Box 39, Folder 39)
  - Commencement Program, 1958; 241713 (Box 39, Folder 40)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1958; 241714 (Box 39, Folder 41)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1959; 241715 (Box 39, Folder 42)
  - Commencement Programs, 1959; 241716 (Box 39, Folder 43)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1959; 241717 (Box 39, Folder 44)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1960; 241718 (Box 39, Folder 45)
  - Commencement Programs, 1960; 241719 (Box 39, Folder 46)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1960; 241720 (Box 39, Folder 47)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1961; 241721 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Programs, 1961; 241722 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1961; 241723 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1962; 241724 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Programs, 1962; 241725 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1962; 241726 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Programs, 1963; 241727 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1963; 241728 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1964; 241729 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Commencement Programs, 1964; 241730 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1964; 241731 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Commencement Programs, 1965; 241732 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1965; 241733 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1966; 241734 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Commencement Programs, 1966; 241735 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1966; 241736 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1967; 241737 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Commencement Programs, 1967; 241738 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1967; 241739 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Commencement Programs, 1968; 241740 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1968; 241741 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1969; 241742 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Commencement Programs, 1969; 241743 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1969; 241744 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Commencement Planning, 1970; 241745 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1970; 241746 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1970; 241747 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Commencement Program, 1971; 241748 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Baccalaureate Ceremony, 1971; 241749 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1972; 241750 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Commencement Program, 1972; 241751 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - NYU Commencement Bulletin, 1973; 241752 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Commencement Program, 1973; 241753 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Commencement Planning, 1974; 241754 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Commencement Planning, 1974; 241755 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Commencement Programs, 1974; 241756 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Commencement Programs, 1975; 241757 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Commencement Programs, 1976; 241758 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Commencement Tickets, 1977; 241759 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Graduation Rosters, 1977; 241760 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Commencement Programs, 1977; 241761 (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Graduation Rosters, 1978; 241762 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Commencement Programs, 1978; 241763 (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Graduation Rosters, 1979; 241764 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Commencement Programs, 1979; 241765 (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Graduation Roster, 1980; 241766 (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Commencement Programs, 1980; 241767 (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - Park Permit, 1980; 241768 (Box 40, Folder 48)
  - Graduation Rosters, 1981; 241769 (Box 40, Folder 49)
  - Commencement Programs, 1981; 241770 (Box 40, Folder 50)
  - Graduation Rosters, 1982; 241771 (Box 40, Folder 51)
  - Commencement Programs, 1982; 241772 (Box 40, Folder 52)
  - Park Permit, 1983; 241773 (Box 40, Folder 53)
  - Graduation Rosters, 1983; 241774 (Box 40, Folder 54)
  - Commencement Programs, 1983; 241775 (Box 40, Folder 55)
  - Park Permit, 1983; 241776 (Box 40, Folder 56)
  - Graduation Rosters, 1984; 241777 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Programs, 1984; 241778 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Park Permit, 1984; 241779 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Fountain Seating and Park Meetings, 1984; 241780 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Park: Agenda Notes and Permit, 1984; 241781 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Graduation Rosters, 1985; 241782 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Programs, 1985; 241783 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Park Permit, 1985; 241784 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Graduation Rosters, 1986; 241785 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Commencement Programs, 1986; 241786 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Park Permit, 1986; 241787 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Graduation Rosters, 1987; 241788 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Commencement Programs, 1987; 241789 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Graduation Rosters, 1988; 241790 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Commencement Programs, 1988; 241791 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Graduation Rosters, 1989; 241792 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Commencement Programs, 1989; 241793 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Commencement Programs, 1990; 241794 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Commencement Planning, 1990; 241795 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Commencement Script, 1990; 241796 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Abbreviated Park Script (Drizzle), 1990; 241797 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Rain Script, 1990; 241798 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Alumni Brunch, 1990; 241799 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Romich Memos, 1990; 241800 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Staff, 1990; 241801 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Set up/Maps, 1990; 241802 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Requisitions, 1990; 241803 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Instructions to Marshals- Entrance, Guest Seating, Live TV, 1990; 241804 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Instructions to Students Procession Marshals, 1990; 241805 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Commencement Programs, 1991; 241806 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Commencement Planning, 1991; 241807 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Commencement Script, 1991; 241808 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Abbreviated Park Script (Drizzle), 1991; 241809 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Rain Script, 1991; 241810 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Alumni Brunch, 1991; 241811 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Memos, 1991; 241812 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Set-up/Maps, 1991; 241813 (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - Staff, 1991; 241814 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Marshal Instructions, 1991; 241815 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Instructions to Student Procession Marshals, 1991; 241816 (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Instructions for Faculty Procession Marshals, 1991; 241817 (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Instructions for Marshals- Entrance, Guest Seating, Live TV, 1991; 241818 (Box 41, Folder 42)
  - Coles Planning, 1991; 241819 (Box 41, Folder 43)
  - Commencement Ticket, 1991; 241820 (Box 41, Folder 44)
  - Board of Trustees Dinner, 1991; 241821 (Box 41, Folder 45)
  - Commencement Directory, 1991; 241822 (Box 41, Folder 46)
  - Commencement Programs, 1992; 241823 (Box 41, Folder 47)
  - Commencement Planning, 1992; 241824 (Box 41, Folder 48)
  - Commencement Script- Oliva, 1992; 241825 (Box 41, Folder 49)
  - Commencement Script, 1992; 241826 (Box 41, Folder 50)
  - Coles Rain Script, 1992; 241827 (Box 41, Folder 51)
  - Coles Rain Script- Oliva, 1992; 241828 (Box 41, Folder 52)
  - Alumni Brunch, 1992; 241829 (Box 41, Folder 53)
  - Catering, 1992; 241830 (Box 41, Folder 54)
  - Romich Memos, 1992; 241831 (Box 41, Folder 55)
  - Requisitions, 1992; 241832 (Box 41, Folder 56)
  - Instructions for Students Procession Marshals, 1992; 241833 (Box 41, Folder 57)
  - Commencement Programs, 1993; 241834 (Box 41, Folder 58)
  - Commencement Planning, 1993; 241835 (Box 41, Folder 59)
  - Commencement Planning, 1993; 241836 (Box 41, Folder 60)
  - Commencement Script- Jops, 1993; 241837 (Box 41, Folder 61)
  - Commencement Script- Pres. Oliva, 1993; 241838 (Box 41, Folder 62)
  - Commencement Script- Abbreviated Park (rain), 1993; 241839 (Box 41, Folder 63)
  - Commencement Script- Snow room (rain), 1993; 241840 (Box 41, Folder 64)
  - Seating Marshals, 1993; 241841 (Box 41, Folder 65)
  - Procession Marshals, 1993; 241842 (Box 41, Folder 66)
  - Catering, 1993; 241843 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Set-up Memos, 1993; 241844 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Trustees Pre-Commencement Dinner, 1993; 241845 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Post-commencement Mailing, 1993; 241846 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Script- revised 5/12/93, 1993; 241847 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Scripts w/ Prologue, 1993; 241848 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Scripts- Synopsis, 1993; 241849 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Commencement Information and Fliers, 1993; 241850 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Commencement Forms, 1993; 241851 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Instructions for Faculty Procession Marshals, 1993; 241852 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Instructions for Students Procession Marshals, 1993; 241853 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Instruction for Marshals- Entrance, Guest Seating, Live TV, 1993; 241854 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Commencement Tickets and Passes, 1993; 241855 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - NYU Today- Commencement, 1993; 241856 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Commencement Programs, 1994; 241857 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Stage Manager's Park Script, 1994; 241858 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Instructions for Faculty Procession Marshals, 1994; 241859 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Instructions for Students Procession Marshals, 1994; 241860 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Instructions for Marshals- Entrance, Guest Seating, Live TV, 1994; 241861 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Commencement Tickets, 1994; 241862 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Commencement Script (annotated), 1994; 241863 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Commencement Directory, 1994; 241864 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Requisitions, 1994; 241865 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Notices, 1994; 241866 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Commencement Script Synopsis, 1994; 241867 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Commencement Script- Snow Room (rain), 1994; 241868 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Stage Manager's Abbreviated Park Script (rain), 1994; 241869 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Abbreviated Park Script (rain), 1994; 241870 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Commencement Instructions Mailing, 1994; 241871 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Commencement Mailing, 1994; 241872 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Commencement Order Forms, 1994; 241873 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Commencement Planning, 1994; 241874 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Commencement Script- Oliva, 1994; 241875 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Commencement Script w/ Cues, 1994; 241876 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Drizzle Script (annotated), 1994; 241877 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Memos, 1994; 241878 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Catering, 1994; 241879 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Set-up/Maps, 1994; 241880 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Staff, 1994; 241881 (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Trustees Dinner, 1994; 241882 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Commencement Programs, 1995; 241883 (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - Commencement Planning, 1995; 241884 (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Valedictory Speech- Momplaisir, 1995; 241885 (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Commencement Script, 1995; 241886 (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - Stage Manager's Park Script, 1995; 241887 (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - Commencement Script- Oliva, 1995; 241888 (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - Abbreviated Park Script (drizzle), 1995; 241889 (Box 42, Folder 47)
  - Snow Script and Set-Up (rain), 1995; 241890 (Box 42, Folder 48)
  - Memos, 1995; 241891 (Box 42, Folder 49)
  - Catering, 1995; 241892 (Box 42, Folder 50)
  - Set-up/Maps, 1995; 241893 (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - Staff, 1995; 241894 (Box 42, Folder 52)
  - Trustee Dinner, 1995; 241895 (Box 42, Folder 53)
  - Instructions to Marshals, 1995; 241896 (Box 42, Folder 54)
  - Commencement Directory, 1995; 241897 (Box 42, Folder 55)
  - Commencement and Grad Alley Programs, Scripts, Tickets, Badges, Hats, and Mailings, 2016 (Box 43, Folder 5-8)
  - Commencement and Grad Alley Programs, Invitations, and Mailings, 2018 (Box 42, Folder 56)
  - Tiffany ink pen with silver torch, 2007
    Scope and Contents
    ID Number: 433. Description: Tiffany ink pen with silver torch. Creator/Donor/Subject: Office of Commencement and Special Events (RG 7.4).
- Unprocessed Banners (Box 55)
  - Unprocessed Accretion 90-019 (Box 115)